I saw a video of Killer Mike and he was telling the congregation, like, if you don't even know how to fish or hunt or grow food, like y'all ain't ready for a revolution.
And I would argue that you can really learn all of those things.
If there's people in your community that know how to do those things, like they can teach the community and it can happen.
What I don't think you can actually learn, though, is like empathy.
And I think the reason that we're not actually ready for a revolution is because we as a people don't even have a shared bottom line on what like literal human decency is.
Like people who you think are good people are completely fine with somebody being supportive of a genocide because they're black.
People who you think are like completely normal people don't see any necessity for the Epstein files to come out.
They're like big whoop.
OK, so the world is run by pedophiles and it's not like we're going to be able to do anything about it.
Like. So there isn't a shared, desired, expressed bottom line for what we consider to be human decency.
Many of our personal relationships fail because we don't have that shared value system amongst each other.
But we don't have like a shared understanding of how to treat each other.
And so then it falls apart.
There's entire swaths of people that you consider to be your community who think it's completely fine that other swaths of people are getting ripped away from their families because they are a member of a cultural group that had members that voted for a particular person.
So if you're wondering, why aren't people waking up?
Why aren't we standing up?
Why aren't we?
That's why.
Because we don't have a shared bottom line on who's worth standing up for.
We are stardust floating up.